favordelivery.com 2018-11-15

# 

##  Privacy Policy 

_Effective February  2017_  
NeighborFavor Inc., a Delaware corporation d/b/a Favor (“ **Favor** ,” “ **our** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **we** “)respects your privacy. We created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect and how we use it, as well as our practices regarding such information.

This Privacy Policy applies to:

  * The website <https://favordelivery.com/> (the “ **Website** ”);
  * Our mobile on-demand ordering service (the “ **Service** ”);
  * Our mobile application(s) we offer in connection with the Service (the “ **App** ”); and
  * Any email, text and other electronic communications between you and the Favor.

This Privacy Policy does _not_ apply to:

  * Information we collect offline or by any other means (such as through other websites or services we may offer); and
  * Information collected by our affiliates or any other third parties, which may have their own privacy policies.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and save it. If you do not agree with it, you should not access the Website or use the Service or the App. By using the Service, the Website, the App or by submitting electronic communications to us, you consent to the practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy.

## What information does Favor collect?

  * **Personal Information.** When we refer to “ **Personal Information** ” in this Privacy Policy, we mean any information by which you may be personally identified or contacted, whether online or offline. When you use the Service or fill out any forms located on the Website or the App, we may collect certain Personal Information from you, such as your first and last name, address/location, email address, phone number, and gender.. Additionally, if you apply to be a runner, we may collect certain other Personal Information from you as further described in our Runner Software Agreement and/or runner policies and procedures. As a customer user or a runner, it is always your choice whether or not to provide Personal Information. If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or use certain features of the Service or the App.
  * **Technical Information.** We may also collect and use technical data and related information, such as information about your device, system and application software, peripherals and other data related to your interactions with the Service (“ **Technical Information** ”). We automatically collect Technical Information through the use of “cookies” and other similar collection technologies, like pixels, web beacons and local storage. The information we collect from these technologies may include your web settings and preferences, website analytics information, device type, phone operating system and push ID. Favor does not consider this information to be Personal Information. Favor owns all Technical Information and may use it for any lawful purpose. Depending on your browser, you may be able to remove and reject cookies from our Website or the Service by changing your browser settings. The default setting of many browsers is set to accept cookies until you change your settings. Please note that if you disable or refuse cookies, certain features of the Website or the Service may become inaccessible or may not function properly.
  * **Location Information.** We also collect information about your geographic location from you or your device, including your country, region, city, zip code, street address, time zone, latitude, longitude, and horizontal position representation information (“ **Location Information** ”).
  * **Social Information.** We may also collect information about you from various third-party services (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and others) through their applicable APIs or otherwise (“ **Social Information** ”).
  * **Tracking and Do Not Track Signals.** We use the Website, the App and the Service to collect information about your activities over time and across third-party websites, applications or other online services (“ **Tracking Information** ”). Your web browser, application platform or device may allow you to opt-out of our collection of Tracking Information by selecting a “do not track” (or similar) setting. However, we do not currently have processes to address those settings or other “do not track” requests, and consequently, cannot guarantee that we will honor such requests. If you do not want us to collect this information, do not use the Website, the App or the Service.

**Order Information and Other Information You Voluntarily Disclose.** Certain features of Service and the App are designed to display Information that you choose to provide to other users (such as texts between customer users and the runners delivering products), or to other third parties (such as merchants from whom you order products). Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Information by ordering products or otherwise providing such Information through the Service or the App (including, for example, if you provide building or security codes to a runner), that Information can be seen by those users or third parties to whom you send that Information. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any Information you choose to submit in connection with these features.

## How does Favor use this Information?

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or in our Terms of Service, Personal Information, Technical Information, Location Information, Social Information and Tracking Information (collectively, “ **Information** ”) that you provide or that we collect will be kept confidential and used to support your relationship with Favor.

We may use your Information, including your Personal Information, as follows:

  * For order fulfillment, billing and delivery purposes.
  * To enable you to participate in interactive features of the Service or the App (such as communications between customer users and runners)
  * To provide services and customer support to you
  * To improve, test, update, and monitor Favor’s products and services for a better user experience.
  * To communicate with you, including about the Service, the App or your account.
  * To market or promote the Service, the App or products and services its of Favor’s third-party partners.
  * For any other purpose we may describe when you provide the Information.

In addition, Favor and its third-party partners may also use the Information to: remember your Information so you will not have to re-enter it during a subsequent visit; help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; diagnose or fix technology problems; and for security and fraud prevention purposes, including identifying and distinguishing between fraudulent and legitimate transactions.

## Information We Share

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Favor does not share, rent or sell your Personal Information with third parties.

Favor or its agents, vendors or contractors may disclose Information, including your Personal Information, to third parties in the following circumstances:

  * To our agents, vendors or contractors that we use to support the internal operations of our business including the Service, the App and the Website and who are required to keep the Information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. This includes our third-party payment processor who processes transactions on our behalf and who is required to treat your Information in accordance with EU Privacy Directive 95/46 and successor (including EU Privacy Regulation 2016/679) and other applicable privacy laws.
  * If required to do so by law, comply with legal process or to comply with a governmental or regulatory request;
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Favor or its agents or contractors;
  * To enforce our Terms of Service or other Favor agreements;
  * To act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service, the App or the Website or the public; and
  * As part of a transaction or potential transaction where Favor merges with another organization, files for bankruptcy, or sells its assets or capital stock.

When you place an order, we will provide the following Information to the runner that fulfills your order: your name, phone number, order details, the merchant whose products you are requesting, and Location Information so the runner can fulfill your order and communicate with you about your order.

If you are a runner, we may share Information related to amounts paid to you with our third-party payment processor and the relevant taxing authorities for tax purposes, as further described in our Runner Software Agreement.

## Security of Your Information

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect the Information. These safeguards include storing your Information on our secure servers behind firewalls and using encryption technology. Through the use of third-party technologies, we collect your credit card information; however, such information is encrypted so it is not visible to Favor. We do not store your credit card information, which is stored and processed by our third-party payment processor vendor. Despite the actions and precautions we take, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the Information and you acknowledge and agree that you transmit it to us at your own risk.

## Third-Party Websites, Services and Technologies ** **

We may provide links to third-party websites on the Website or in other communications to you. These links may appear as a specific domain name or URL or may be activated by clicking on an advertisement or other icon or graphic. Please be aware that other websites and services, including the websites of third parties that you connect with through the Service, may collect personally identifiable information about you. We cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of any third-party websites, services or applications. We encourage you to carefully review their terms of use, privacy policies, and any other legal notifications before using or providing information through such websites, services or applications.

Further, the Service may employ third party technologies that require you to accept such third party’s terms. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third-party technologies.

## International Transfers

Information collected from you may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Favor or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities. If you are accessing the Service from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your data to the United States and processing globally. By providing your Information, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Children’s Privacy

The Website, the App and the Service are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect Information from children under 13. If you believe that we may have collected Information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us at [contact@favordelivery.com](mailto:contact@favordelivery.com).

## Information Choices and Changes

We may need to communicate with you about the Service and the App, and we would like to make certain commercial offers available to you from time to time. _As such, you consent to receive commercial messages (whether by phone, email, text or push notifications) from us or our third party partners, and acknowledge and agree that your primary phone numbers and email addresses and other information may be used for the purpose of initiating commercial messages_. We will allow you to opt-out of receiving commercial messages, but in order to stop receiving any messages from us whatsoever (including administrative messages regarding the Service or messages that are primarily about transactions enabled via the Service), you will need to terminate your account.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

This is our entire Privacy Policy and it replaces any earlier version. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version on the Website or through the Service or the App, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically. If we make material changes to our practices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information, we will notify you via e-mail to the email address you provide to us and/or through a notice on the Website home page or via the Service or the App.

When we do change the Privacy Policy, we will also revise the effective date. Your continued use of the Service or the App after such date constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

## Contacting Favor

For questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at NeighborFavor Inc., 1705 Guadalupe Street Austin, Suite 300, TX 78701, [(855) 623-3287](tel: +1\(855\)623-3287) and [contact@favordelivery.com](mailto:contact@favordelivery.com).
